rational I'm out of it started with a robbery a
PS3 swiped from his nephew and never returned and now
-- just has a kick starter project for an open
source tracking device. With 54 days ago he's about 2000
dollars away from being fully -- it first developed is
a video game console tracker for the PS3 -- we
-- base system has gone from that's. To this. The
smaller board is what churches is seeking funding to produce
on board he placed -- GPS cell phone chip connections
for a lithium polymer battery. And a few other essentials
when combined with an antenna and a battery those things
are tracking taxing machine so -- PS Bristol and you
her press coordinate by sending a text to the board
that would respond with a link to Google map. That
in -- event of course be turned over to authorities
or if you're feeling brave you can also program the
device to tell you how fast and in what direction
it's moving. Sucking out just in case you wanted to
be involved in high speed high tech chase really go
as -- explains this device can be almost anything you
want. This project is all open source so you'll have
full access to all the code. And his dramatics to
you can program the device to do whatever you wanted
to do to back it residents kick start page and
happy -- For national out of.